http://www.hopkinsmedicalproducts.com/service/a/privacy-policy/

Shop All
3M™ Littmann® Stethoscopes Bags & Totes Blood Pressure Monitoring Custom Logo Printing Diagnostics DME Equipment & Instruments Go Pink Infection Control Nursing Supplies Patient Care Pulse Oximeters Scales & Measurement Starter Kits Stethoscopes Thermometers Vehicle Organization and Accessories
Home Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Hopkins Medical Products and HopkinsMedicalProducts.com are committed to the privacy of its customers. This Privacy Policy applies to all customers, including California residents in compliance to the California Consumer Privacy Act., and describes the information collected through our websites and employees.
Data Collection Information we collect directly from you includes your billing address, shipping address, contact information, e-mail address, payment information and comments and suggestions. For each visitor to our website, the information we collect indirectly from you includes your IP address, browsing history, location and order activity while on our websites. Our web server automatically recognizes the domain name and e-mail address (where possible). The information gained is used to improve order and request fulfillment, improving website operations, site functionality and navigation. We use cookies to record session information, such as items that customers add to their shopping cart, and to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit.
Customer Contact We collect only the information you choose to share. How Information is used
Direct Mail – If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. Email – If you supply us with your email address you may receive e-mail contact from us in the future informing you of new products, and services provided available. Phone – Customers who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. In addition, they may also receive telephone contacts in the future with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events.
Opting Out
If you do not wish to be contacted via telephone, mailings or email, please contact us at the phone number or e-mail link listed below. Please be sure to provide us with your exact name and address.
Sharing Customer Data We occasionally make our mailing list available to companies whose products and services might interest you.
You can have your name put on our do-not-share list by calling us at the number provided below, e-mailing us at the belowaddress or clicking Do Not Sell My Info. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of the change. If you are concerned about how your information is used, we encourage you to check back at our website periodically. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to information (e.g., customer number, name, address or password) that we maintain about them. Customers can access this information by e-mailing or writing to us at the addresses listed below. We offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Children's Online Policy
It is the responsibility of Hopkins Medical Products and HopkinsMedicalProducts.com to safeguard the online privacy of all its visitors, including children. We do not knowingly collect information about children or sell products to children. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not consciously gather any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you must have a parent or guardian aid you in using HopkinsMedicalProducts.com. Security When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and may notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us at the below addresses or phone number. Hopkins Medical Products
Circulation Department
6850 Southbelt Dr.
Caledonia MI 49316
www.hopkinsmedicalproducts.com
Phone 800-835-1995 Email customerservice@hopkinsmedical.net
Email Sign Up Subscribe TODAY and Save $10 on your next order!
Sign Up
Exclusive savings Special promotions Sneak peeks on new products Contest notifications
Company Information
About Us Privacy Policy W-9 Information News Resource Center Videos Customer Testimonials Terms of Sale
Customer Service
Contact Us Express Order Customer Service FAQs Pricing Shipping Returns Custom Medical Bags Bag Warranty Bag Cleaning Instructions Accessibility
Additional Information
Request Catalog Download Catalog E-Mail Sign-Up Website Help Healthcare Bag Technique Pulse Oximetry Saves Lives Antimicrobial Medical Bags
Call Us at 1-800-835-1995
© 2020 Hopkins Medical Products, All rights reserved.
